[{"answer": "For once in a while I'm extremely grateful for your British roots.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "Most of his party thinks he's crackers (ph)?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "Smart and remarkably -- we had a really good blunt relationship.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "What do you really think of Vladimir Putin?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Brutally blunt.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "How blunt?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, first, all the problems are probably being intensified by the economic challenges we face.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "What is your take on, on where we are?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think it's an interesting commentary on the world in which we're living that admitting that the holocaust occurred qualified as being a moderate.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "How much do you trust him?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "No, we don't have to believe it.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "And it's just going to happen?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Smart and remarkably -- we had a really good blunt relationship.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What was he like behind close doors away from, you know, that's with the public utterances?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Brutally blunt.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "ORGAN: How blunt?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "No he did not.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Did Putin ever renege on a personal agreement he made to you?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "He kept his word and all the deal that we made.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "So behind closed doors, he could be trusted?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Can you just share with us a little bit about why you think that's so important?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "The day after tomorrow, my wife because she's had more experience.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Well, coming to your family as you're talking women in the workforce, who do you think might make the better president, your wife or your daughter?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Can you put as all out of our misery?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "We worked it out when he was trying to run me out of town.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "What is the ways first, you and Newt Gingrich eventually worked it up between you -- how do you get stuff done in this dysfunctional Washington?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Because consistently, with the single exception of my getting reelected in 1996, the people who agree with us on the gun issue have not been able to protect the people they elect.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Why did they do that?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "No, it is not.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Isn't it about political (ph) courage?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "He does.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Does he do a good Bono impression?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "He does.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "He does?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "It was pretty good.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Now, first of all, what was your reaction when you heard Bono pretending to be you?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I think the point of the film is really to first of all, to really listen and see -- just to see what are these brilliant minds thinking.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "What is the point of this film?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "You know, what I think that maybe in a better question for you to answer as a man.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Sharon, would the world be a less dangerous, less warmongering place if more women run countries?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Well, for me, it's -- has a little bit of the difference between erotica and pornography.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Is that still unfair?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not so much expressing an opinion here.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "And was Miley into that?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "TONE: You know, I think that when we're looking at a pop and rock entertainment, and someone who's pop and rock entertainer, there's a question of this -- of entertainment.", "docId": "130927pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "What do you think, Sharon?", "qSentId": 437}]